Before
之前
Cabbage
卷心菜
This is a cabbage
这是白菜
It's called something
叫做东西
I'm so sorry
我很抱歉
I don't understand the point of ice and snow
我不明白冰雪的重点
Skip the singer always wash your vegetables
跳过歌手总是洗菜
Because it looks not right
因为看起来不对
Go for it
去吧
I am reading the West
我在读西方
Turn off the lights
把开关关掉
Roll It All app
滚动全部应用
I know this doesn't look great right now
我知道这现在看起来不太好
We have
我们有
Let us a whole head of iceberg
让我们全力以赴
Tasteless
无味
You can probably get the 99 Cent store and you would pay like for 99 in a bag
您可能可以在99 Cent商店中购物，并且要在袋子中支付99美元
30 seconds of handsome and thinking about your ex
30秒的帅气和思考你的前任
Salad
沙拉
Can you use
你能用吗
I take off
我起飞
Like the top players in it's the best
就像顶尖球员一样
Is there amazing
有没有很棒的
Straight down the middle
中间直下
This is
这是
No one wants to eat salad
没有人想吃沙拉
With big pieces letters
大件字母
Is loaded up with bacon bits
装满培根钻头
Blue cheese dressing this is one way to do it
蓝纹奶酪酱是做到这一点的一种方法
Not too big not too small
不太大也不太小
Play Steven mother truck
玩史蒂芬妈妈卡车
Pause
暂停
Where do you chop some lettuce SO31 ahead of iceberg
你在冰山之前在哪里切一些生菜SO31
Things that roll around the heart and the very first thing I want to do when I'm having lettuce onion tomato or any
当我生菜洋葱番茄或其他任何东西时，会在心脏周围滚动的事情和我要做的第一件事
Is the earth flat
地球平吗
Score of the weather's of and put that facing the ceiling in my very first the entire point is the
天气的得分，而我首先面对天花板的问题是
Something Blue
蓝色的东西
Iceberg or any other heading that if you have a look on that actually going to work
Iceberg或其他标题，如果您对此有实际的了解
Everything together
一切都在一起
I'm just going to
我只是去
Turn it into 2 Quarter
变成2季度
That's it
而已
I have the option then I could maybe slice really thin slices of lettuce like
我可以选择将生菜切成薄片
Put it on top of something like that
把它放在这样的东西之上
What I want to do is then go ahead and one more time
然后我想做的是再进行一次
In your nearest then I'm going right through the core
在离您最近的地方，我将直通核心
That's going to keep it from falling apart
这样可以防止它崩溃
Travelling tonight
今晚旅行
Bitesize pizza
比萨饼
Can I have my wireless chart
我可以拿无线图表吗
Before I turn this into a nice salad
在我把它变成精美的沙拉之前
I need to wash it
我要洗一下
Before the chocolate but how you gonna get in between the waves that why so it is just like this
在巧克力之前，但是您如何进入海浪之间，为什么如此
Transferred to a salad spinner and dryer
转移到沙拉旋转器和烘干机
There is our lettuce for salad
我们有沙拉生菜
Lettuce
生菜
Add server printer in the shaft
在竖井中添加服务器打印机
Reselling
倒卖
Call Aberdeen
致电Aberdeen